<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Rodrigo Müller</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Rodrigo Müller</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2022 21:29:01 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Theme Documentation - Basics</title>
      <link>/projects/theme-documentation-basics/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 21:29:01 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/theme-documentation-basics/</guid>
      <description>Gokarna is an opinionated theme with a focus on minimalism and simplicity.
Installation The following steps are here to help you initialize your new website. If you don’t know Hugo at all, we strongly suggest you learn more about it by following this great documentation for beginners.
a. Create Your Project Hugo provides a new command to create a new website:
hugo new site my_website cd my_website b. Install the Theme The theme’s repository is: https://github.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recital de Piano - Luis Felipe Oliveira</title>
      <link>/posts/recital_piano/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2022 21:29:01 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/recital_piano/</guid>
      <description>Solista do próximo concerto da Osli, Luis Felipe Oliveira realiza recital no dia 22 de março  Garanta Seu Ingresso!
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Markdown Syntax Guide</title>
      <link>/projects/markdown-syntax/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/markdown-syntax/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This article offers a sample of basic Markdown syntax that can be used in Hugo content files, also it shows whether basic HTML elements are decorated with CSS in a Hugo theme.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Emoji Support</title>
      <link>/projects/emoji-support/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Oct 2020 17:55:28 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/emoji-support/</guid>
      <description>Emoji can be enabled in a Hugo project in a number of ways.
The emojify function can be called directly in templates or Inline Shortcodes.
To enable emoji globally, set enableEmoji to true in your site configuration and then you can type emoji shorthand codes directly in content files.
These begin and end with a colon and include the code of an emoji:
Gone camping! {?:}tent: Be back soon. That is so funny!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Próximo Concerto da Orquestra Sinfônica de Limeira!</title>
      <link>/posts/proximo_concerto/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2022 23:39:49 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/proximo_concerto/</guid>
      <description>Garanta Seu Ingresso!
 A Orquestra Sinfônica de Limeira apresenta, sob regência do Maestro Rodrigo Müller, o “Concerto de Abertura da Temporada 2022”, com a presença do solista Luis Felipe Oliveira (piano).
Natural de Gravatá, interior de Pernambuco, Luis Felipe Oliveira é formado “cum laude” no curso de Bacharelado em Piano na Universidade Federal de Pernambuco, na classe do prof. Dr. Antonio Nigro (Brasil-Alemanha) e atualmente estuda na “Academia Internacional de Música Aquiles Delle Vigne” em Coimbra, Portugal, na classe do Maestro Aquiles Delle Vigne.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/osli/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/osli/</guid>
      <description>Contate a Orquestra Sinfônica de Limeira  Facebook   Instagram   Youtube   Email   Site  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Aulas</title>
      <link>/aulas/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/aulas/</guid>
      <description>Aulas de Oboé  Valor R$ 60,00/hora
 Aulas de Flauta Transversal  Valor R$ 60,00/hora
 Aulas de Flauta Doce  Valor R$ 60,00/hora
 Aulas de Teoria Musical  Realizar orçamento
 Aulas de Regência  Realizar orçamento
 Obs: todos os valores e formas de pagamentos podem ser negociados.
Entre em contato!  https://contate.me/rodrigomuller (Whatsapp)
  rmoboe@gmail.com (Gmail)
  https://web.facebook.com/maestrorodrigomuller/ (Facebook)
  https://www.instagram.com/maestrorodrigomuller/ (Instagram)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blüdhaven</title>
      <link>/projects/bludhaven/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/bludhaven/</guid>
      <description>History Blüdhaven was a former whaling town, which was officially incorporated as a &amp;ldquo;Commonwealth&amp;rdquo; in 1912. The town had a generally poor socio-economic populace, owing in part to failed efforts to transform itself into a manufacturing and shipping center.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Consertos de Instrumentos</title>
      <link>/lutheria/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/lutheria/</guid>
      <description>Entre em contato para um orçamento:  https://contate.me/rodrigomuller (Whatsapp)
  rmoboe@gmail.com (Gmail)
  https://web.facebook.com/maestrorodrigomuller/ (Facebook)
  https://www.instagram.com/maestrorodrigomuller/ (Instagram)
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Currículo Artístico</title>
      <link>/sobre/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/sobre/</guid>
      <description>Músico instrumentista, arranjador, diretor musical e regente, Rodrigo Müller foi oboísta da Orquestra Sinfônica de Rio Claro e Orquestra Sinfônica Municipal de Americana, também foi músico convidado de importantes orquestras como; Orquestra Jazz Sinfônica do Estado de São Paulo, Orquestra Sinfônica do Conservatório Musical de Tatuí, Orquestra Sinfônica de Ribeirão Preto e Orquestra Filarmônica Brasileira. Foi músico integrante da Banda Sinfônica do Estado de São Paulo de 2001 até sua extinção em 2017.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hydra</title>
      <link>/projects/hydra/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/hydra/</guid>
      <description>Motto Cut off one head and two will take their place</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tatooine</title>
      <link>/projects/tatooine/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/tatooine/</guid>
      <description>A long time ago in a galaxy far, far away&amp;hellip;. A project was planned, but never completed</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>